Hello. Where are you?
We're eating
Boiled Fish with Pickled Cabbage.
Okay, I'm coming.
But we're with Gu Yu.
Then you guys eat. I'm not going.
Don't get exposed.
Granny, you, and me
went to the amusement park together.
I left early for an emergency
- on the way back.
- Granny, try the fish.
Okay.
Come on. Try this.
You haven't told us how you found us.
You said you were eating boiled fish.
There were only a few
boiled fish restaurants nearby.
With persistence,
I finally found this place.
Why are you so persistent?
Come on. Try this.
Are we exposed?
I'm asking you.
Why are you grinning like that?
A young man cares about a girl so much.
What else could it be?
Granny, I'm over 30 years old,
not a young man anymore.
In my eyes, you're both young.
Granny, you got us wrong.
I don't like being trapped,
and neither does he, right?
Yes.
We can't be together.
I see.
It's hard for you to get married.
Yes.
Maybe you don't have to get married.
You can keep dating like this.
Granny, here's to you.
I want beer.
I'm 72 years old.
I'm old enough to drink.
Half a glass.
Granny, half a glass.
- Cheers.
Wish you two be happy and in love forever.
Granny.
Why did you drink
when you knew you'd drive?
Where do you live?
FANCY GARDEN
Ready to go, 9.5 kilometers,
around 21 minutes.
We're in the same direction.
Why do you like SUVs?
I love nature and often go
to the outskirts for sketching.
It's more convenient. What about you?
I love nature and often go
to the outskirts for animals.
It's more convenient.
Don't imitate me.
You're definitely drunk.
Why are you staring at me?
You look pretty.
So pretty.
Stop looking at me, or I'll get angry.
You look pretty when you're angry.
So pretty.
Don't be serious with a drunk man.
I'm not drunk.
Okay, you're not drunk.
Don't throw up this time.
I'm not drunk.
I'm just happy.
For what?
I'm happy
because a genius designed
and produced this Tank 300.
Because our brilliant ancestors
invented wine
9,000 years ago.
You're definitely drunk.
You're talking nonsense.
I'm happy because
we both bought
Tank 300.
I'm happy because I got drunk,
got in the wrong car,
and met you.
Turn left, enter the inner road,
and turn left again.
Did you choose the wrong address?
Why are we at my place?
Not wrong.
Drunk man, you're clearly wrong.
Where do you live?
Not wrong.
I'll head home after you get home.
My car will arrive in five minutes.
Are you really sober?
I'm just so happy
that I feel like I'm drunk.
I'm going home. Bye.
Lin Yuan!
Let's be together.
Not for marriage,
just
a relationship.
I thought you wanted to get married.
I do.
However,
is marriage really necessary
for one's life?
Right now,
I just want
to be in a relationship with you,
without thinking about marriage.
It's tiring to be my boyfriend.
I don't believe in love or marriage
or that a relationship can last long.
I love my career more.
Do you like me?
You like me.
Then, it's enough.
Is that enough?
It's enough
for me.
Have you heard?
Mr. Tang is taking a long vacation.
Mr. Tang took a day off,
but I didn't hear
he'd take a long vacation.
Something's wrong with his eyes.
I heard it was serious.
Mr. Zhang from Vandai
was telling the truth.
Will our company be affected?
Where did you get the news?
It must be fake.
I heard it from Lin. It must be real.
We have an advanced medical system.
Even if he's ill, he'll be cured.
Mr. Zhou and Mr. Gu
will take care of everything.
We don't need to worry.
Had I known he was so vulnerable,
I wouldn't have let Quan Shengtang
die in front of him.
TANG QI
Hello.
I went to see a psychiatrist.
What did the doctor say?
The doctor said
a mental issue
should be solved
by psychological treatment.
When Quan Shengtang died by accident,
you were also there.
The doctor told me
to spend more time with you
to adjust my emotion
and restore my eyesight.
The doctor told you
to spend time with me?
It sounds unreliable.
If it's not convenient for you,
you can reject me.
No problem at all.
We don't have much work to do.
I'll take a day off and go to your place.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
The doctor…
told me something else.
Go ahead.
We must cure your eyes.
No matter what it is,
I'll try my best to help you.
I suddenly became blind
at Granny Quan's place.
The doctor also told me
to spend some time with her
to get over it
and restore my eyesight.
But Granny Quan just lost her grandson.
She's also in pain.
How could I ask her for a favor?
Don't worry.
This is for your disease.
Granny Quan will understand.
I'll talk to her.
I can pick her up and go to your place.
You're so kind.
Why did he sound so strange?
The blindness even changed
his personality.
Yuan, I need help.
CASE FORMULATION AND ANALYSIS
IN COUNSELING AND PSYCHOTHERAPY
You're here.
Why did you open the door without asking?
The gate is wide open.
Aren't you afraid of bad buys?
I'm a little slow.
I didn't want you to wait,
so I opened it in advance.
I brought Granny Quan here.
Granny, come in.
He looks pitiful.
Your shoe.
Right here.
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
Granny, sit on the couch.
Don't be polite.
I can take care of myself.
Granny,
your voice
sounds different.
I caught a cold last night.
I'm having a sore throat.
You're not feeling well,
and you came to visit me.
I'm so sorry.
Your eye disease was caused by…
Quan.
I should be responsible.
Don't feel guilty.
As long as you can restore your eyesight,
we're willing to do anything for you.
Doctor
did give me a piece of advice.
What advice?
Real-life desensitization.
Real…
What is real-life desensitization?
What is it?
It's also called quick desensitization.
It's a variation
of systematic desensitization.
Use the actual stimulus
that triggers the reaction
to replace the imagined stimulus.
Accompany the patient
and use a series of situations
to make the patient feel uncomfortable
until the patient is no longer
nervous about or sensitive
to the situations.
Isn't this scene recreation?
The cause of your blindness
is Quan Shengtang's sudden death.
Then it's…
I'm Su Chengcheng.
I'm Tang Qi.
I'm Quan Shengtang.
When I was talking to Tang Qi,
Quan Shengtang came.
He'd been mentally vulnerable
because of his research.
During our conversation,
he was suddenly informed
that he got the research fund
he'd longed for.
Then he was overjoyed
and couldn't stop laughing,
which caused
the stress-induced cardiomyopathy.
Quan Shengtang! Quan Shengtang!
Are you okay?
What happened?
Wake up!
What happened? Wake up!
Quan Shengtang!
If Quan Shengtang and Granny Quan
didn't exist,
how could I have seen
Quan Shengtang and his grandma?
No.
What's wrong?
That day,
Quan Shengtang came from behind me.
Mr. Tang.
Something's wrong.
What's wrong?
Quan Shengtang's voice
wasn't this close to me.
Well, here…
How about this?
Here.
What about now?
And here.
Enough.
That's the right place.
Mr. Tang.
Tang Qi?
Are you okay?
This…
Tang Qi…
Quan Shengtang…
You died…
because of me!
It was an accident.
It's not your fault.
If I hadn't insisted on confronting
you and Su Chengcheng,
you wouldn't have come out to see me
when you didn't want to.
I'm sorry!
This…
Tang… Tang Qi.
Water… Water…
Water…
I'll get some water.
Tang Qi, I understand
why you wanted to see me.
It was an accident.
It wasn't your fault.
Water.
Tang Qi, have some water.
Come on.
Have some water.
Who are you?
I…
I'm Su Chengcheng.
Calm down.
This is just acting.
Stop acting.
Get out.
Leave my house!
Tang Qi…
Get out!
Okay.
We… We're leaving.
Let's go.
Calm down! Don't hurt yourself!
Calm down!
The quick desensitization
didn't work for him.
He didn't get over it
but became more excited.
You should go back first.
I'm a little worried about him.
Even if you're worried,
there's no point
in waiting outside his house.
Stop playing.
Who is the traitor in our company?
We'll find out soon.
They kept an eye on Tang at the fair.
This is…
They've gone too far!
YUAN
I need to take my girlfriend's call.
You can leave.
You…
So cheesy.
- Hello.
- Tang Qi's mental issue is very serious.
He even went crazy
and kicked us out.
Chengcheng is worried about him.
Why don't you come over?
Where are you?
I'm near Tang Qi's house
with Chengcheng.
Okay, I'm coming.
Gu Yu will come here.
Don't be too worried.
If I tell Tang Qi
that Quan Shengtang doesn't exist
and that his death was a show,
will he recover?
Tang Qi is smart.
If he finds out Quan Shengtang is fake,
he'll soon think about
Su Miao and Fang Jin.
What will you do then?
Tell him the truth?
I'm willing to do anything
to cure his eyes.
If he finds out Su Miao, his first love,
and Fang Jin, the girl
he risked his life to protect,
are both fake,
will it drive him crazy?
We've figured it out.
Su Miao,
Fang Jin,
and Quan Shengtang
are all fake.
They are all fake.
This is unbelievable.
In 1917,
the first drone was invented,
but it didn't go public
until decades later.
The spray-on fabric technology
invented by Manel Torres is mature,
but it might take decades
for common people
to wear such clothes.
It seems Su Chengcheng
got a filter product leaked from a lab.
Su Chengcheng fooled me again and again.
But I trusted her
like a fool.
When Su Miao died,
I was heartbroken.
When I fell in love with Fang Jin,
I felt guilty and painful,
like a fool.
I can't believe I cried
for the disappearance
of Fang Jin's
other personality.
I must be the stupidest person
in the world.
You're right.
You were fooled.
However,
perhaps you can view this
from a different angle.
Su Miao, Fang Jin,
and Quan Shengtang,
none of them died.
No matter what,
no death
is the best result.
I'll pick up my girlfriend.
You and Su Chengcheng
should sort this out.
Are you hungry?
Close the net.
TANG QI
I'll go over there.
Did you visit Tang Qi?
Get in. I'll tell you.
Why do I need to get in?
Tang Qi will come out.
Do you want to see him?
What is he coming out?
Does he know Chengcheng is there?
He'll know when he comes out.
Let Tang Qi and Su Chengcheng
sort this out.
Will they be in trouble?
One is smart, and the other is strong.
Someone else will be in trouble.
Fasten the seat belt.
Mr. Gu…
Well, I'm a little tired.
I'm not joining you for dinner.
You must be tired after resting all day.
Slow down.
Here. Your clothes.
Thanks.
LIGHT YELLOW MID-LAYER
4 UNDERPANTS
1 UNDERPANTS
EXPRESS
Su Chengcheng.
How do you know it's me?
I…
I'm just passing by.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Where are you going? Let me walk with you.
Go to the park for a stroll.
Tang Qi,
do you have any enemies
or owe anyone money?
I don't have any debt.
Many people are jealous of me.
But I have no enemies.
Then who are they?
Why don't we go this way?
Yes, go straight.
No problem.
There are no obstacles in front.
Yes.
Put the cane away.
What's wrong?
I'm tired.
Tired?
There's a bench. Let's sit there.
I saw them coming this way.
- Where are they?
- They just disappeared.
Go over there, and I'll search this area.
I'll go to the restroom. Wait for me here.
Don't run around.